No, Wil Wheaton
is Sheldon's mortal enemy.
(Amy:)- Mortal enemy?
- Mm-hm.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I know you're a bit
of a left-handed monkey wrench but...
(Amy:)- You really have a mortal enemy?
- ln fact, I have 61 of them.
(Sheldon:)- Would you like to see the list?
- Oh, say no, say no, say no, say no.
(Sheldon:)You just got off the list.
Would you like back on it?
(Sheldon:)This'll just take a moment.
It's on a five and a quarter inch floppy.
- A floppy disk?
- Well, I started the list when I was 9.
(Amy:)How did wil wheaton get on the list?
(All:)Oh, God.
Come on.
As a child, I Ioved Wesley Crusher...
(Sheldon:)...Wil Wheaton's character
on Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)So I drove for hours by bus
to a Star Trek convention...
(Sheldon:)...at which Wil Wheaton
was scheduled to appear...
(Sheldon:)...so that I could get
my Wesley Crusher action figure signed.
(Sheldon:)But he never showed...
(Sheldon:)...because apparently,
it was "cooler" for him...